Guide to the Seattle Teachers' Association Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- SERIES X: RECORDS OF ACTIVITIES WITH AFFILIATED ORGANIZATIONS, 1953-1969 (Box-folder 13/9-14/56)
  - WEA Department of Classroom Teachers meetings, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 14/25)
  - WEA Association of Classroom Teachers spring business meeting, 1969 (Box-folder 14/26)
  - Reports, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 14/27)
  - Reports, 1960 (Box-folder 14/28)
  - Reports, 1961 (Box-folder 14/29)
  - Reports, 1962 (Box-folder 14/30)
  - Reports, 1963 (Box-folder 14/31)
  - Reports, 1964 (Box-folder 14/32)
  - Reports, 1965 (Box-folder 14/33)
  - Reports, 1966 (Box-folder 14/34)
  - Reports, 1968 (Box-folder 14/35)
  - WEA Representative Assembly reports, 1958 (Box-folder 14/36)
  - WEA Representative Assembly reports, 1959 (Box-folder 14/37)
  - WEA Representative Assembly reports, 1960 (Box-folder 14/38)
  - WEA Representative Assembly reports, 1961 (Box-folder 14/39)
  - WEA Representative Assembly reports, 1963 (Box-folder 14/40)
  - WEA Representative Assembly reports, 1964 (Box-folder 14/41)
  - WEA Representative Assembly reports, 1965 (Box-folder 14/42)
  - News releases, 1960-1967 (Box-folder 14/43)
  - WEA newsletter: Capitol Recap, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 14/44)
  - WEA newsletter: Legislative Horizons, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 14/45)
  - WEA newsletter: VIP Vitamins, 1959-1963 (Box-folder 14/46)
  - WEA newsletter: Washington Educators in Action, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 14/47)
  - WEA newsletter: WEA Legislative Outlook, 1965 (Box-folder 14/48)
  - WEA membership, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 14/49)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, 1959-1965 (Box-folder 14/50)
  - Correspondence, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 14/51)
  - Delegate lists, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 14/52)
  - Financial reports, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 14/53)
  - Legislation, 1958-1963 (Box-folder 14/54)
  - Political Unity of State Leaders in Education (P.U.L.S.E.), 1966-1967 (Box-folder 14/55)
  - Miscellaneous, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 14/56)
- SERIES XI: Ephemera, 1958-1968 (Box-folder 15/1-15/7)
  - Ephemera (part 1 of 7), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 15/1)
  - Ephemera (part 2 of 7), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 15/2)
  - Ephemera (part 3 of 7), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 15/3)
  - Ephemera (part 4 of 7), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 15/4)
  - Ephemera (part 5 of 7), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 15/5)
  - Ephemera (part 6 of 7), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 15/6)
  - Ephemera (part 7 of 7), 1958-1968 (Box-folder 15/7)